Guide to the University of Chicago Department of Anthropology Records 1929-1997
University of Chicago Library
- Series VII: Administration
  - Evolutionary Anthropology Training Grant, 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Institutional Grant Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - University- Memos and Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - The Society of the Sigma XI, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Meeting Material Pending Future Use, 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Division of Social Sciences, Dean of the Faculty, 1957-1972 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - University Printing Department, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Nanterre Exchange, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Division of Social Sciences, Annual Report to the Dean, 1963-1973 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Biology Department, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1971-1973 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Tax Exemption for Research Assistants, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Evolutionary Anthropology Training Grant, 1972-1974 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Transportation and Messenger Service, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Behavioral Sciences Training Grant, 1970-1974 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Meetings I, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meetings II, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Committee for Student Affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Visiting Evaluation Committee, 1970-1975 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Publications Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - University of Brasilia, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Anthropological Library, 1970-1975 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Departmental Surveys I, 1973-1975 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Dean, Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Visiting Committee, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Center for Urban Studies, 1965-1975 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - University Safety Coordinator, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Meetings I, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Meetings II, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Department History, Degrees Awarded 1897-1975, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Models of and For Various Routine Handouts from Chairman, 1966-1976 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - ISIMILA, 1974-1976 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Chairman Correspondence, General Memos, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Division- Committee on Rights of Human Subjects, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Divisional Master's Program, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meetings I, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Meetings II, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - College-Biological Sciences Collegiate Division, 1974-1976 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Films, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Reza-Shah Kabir University, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Biological Anthropology, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Work Study, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Trésor de La Langue Francaise, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Divisional Executive Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Divisional Executive Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Divisional Executive Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - College- ASHUM Program, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - University, Honorary Degrees, 1955-1977 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Department. Meetings- Minutes, 1971-1977 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Meetings I, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meetings II, 1976-1977 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Publications Committee, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Advising Loads, 1968-1978 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - AAA Committee on Women, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Department Luncheons (Quad Club),, 1969-1978 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Middle Eastern Studies, 1975,1978 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Divisional Executive Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Master- SSCD, 1975-1978 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence with Dean Kruskal, 1975-1978 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Meetings I, 1977-1978 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Meetings II, 1977-1978 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Division of Social Sciences- Building 50th Anniversary, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1977-1979 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Division-National Humanities Institute, 1978-1979 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Divisional Visiting Committee, 1975-1979 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Chinese Visitors, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Chairman's Annual Reports, 1975-1979 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Social Sciences- Language Lab, 1973-1979 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Field Museum, 1962-1979 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Announcements, 1973-1979 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Nelson Bay Cave Artifacts, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - University- Plant Operations, 1973-1979 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Bradburn Committee on Enrollment, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Meetings I, 1978-1979 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Meetings II, 1978-1979 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - University- Provost- Researches Under Way, 1972-1980 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Fanton Campaign- Fund Raising, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - [Baker] Commission on Graduate Education, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Poverty Research, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - College- Physical Sciences, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1979-1980 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Native American Fund, 1980-1981 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - NRC Assessment of Research/Doctoral Programs, 1980-1981 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Divisional Executive Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Division of Social Sciences- Divisional Master's Program, 1970-1981 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - University- Committee on Awards and Prizes, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - University- Extension, 1970-1981 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Student Faculty Liaison Committee, 1974-1981 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Student Faculty Liaison Committee, 1974-1981 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Meetings I, 1974-1981 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meetings II, 1974-1981 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Meetings III, 1974-1981 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Committee on the Quality of Life in Haskell Hall, 1979-1981 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Cast Collection, 1971-1982 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Divisional Executive Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Divisional Executive Committee, Pending, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Campaign for the Arts and Sciences, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Division of Social Sciences- M.A. Programs by Committees (Latin America and Middle East),, 1978-1982 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Chairman, R. Nicholas Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Fred Eggan Dinner, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Minutiae Memos, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Schoenbrod Fund and Collection, 1977-1982 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Equipment and Services (Computer),, 1969-1983 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Jamake Highwater, 1980-1983 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Mailings to Admitted Students, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Baker Commission on Graduate Education, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Joint Anthropology- Linguistics Program, 1973-1983 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Divisional Executive Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - College/Departmental Liaison, 1960-1983 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Honorary Degree- A.F.C. Wallace, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - [Baker] Commission on Graduate Education, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Fellowship and Research, 1975-1984 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Computer Accounts, 1983-1984 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Anthropology Graduate Students, 1982-1984 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Visiting Committee, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Division of Social Sciences- Faculty Meetings, 1969, 1975, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Decanal Matters, 1980-1984 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - College- College Council Minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Department. Admin.- LSE and UC Exchange, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Social Science Symposium- C.P. Taylor, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Joint B.A./M.A. Program in Anthropology, 1959-1985 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - University Alumni Office, 1977-1985 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Office of the Registrar, 1977-1985 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Greenstone Report (Size and Composition of the U of C),, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Division of Social Sciences- Geography Department, 1985-1986 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - University- Housing, 1977, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Quality of Life in Haskell Hall, 1979-1986 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, Memos, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Departmental Surveys, 1975-1988 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Division of Social Sciences- Visiting Committee, 1978-1988 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Announcements for Graduate Program of Study, 1986-1988 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - China Exchange, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Division of Social Sciences- Divisional Executive Committee, 1969-1989 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - University- Office of the Secretary of the Faculties, 1975-1989 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - University- News and Information 1960-1989 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, Memos, 1988-1989 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Student Teaching, 1981-1990 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Recent Publications, 1980-1990 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, Memos, 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Division of Social Sciences Reports, 1976, 1978, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - College, Student Teaching Guidelines, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - University, Honorary Degrees, 1979-1990 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - University Library (Regenstein), 1965-1990 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Department. Admin-Meetings, Minutes, Memos, 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - University Centennial, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - University Computation Center, Newsletter and Memos, 1959-1991 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - University Office of Legal Council, 1982-1991 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Provost's Office, 1969-1991 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - University Office of Special Events, 1983-1991 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Social Science Collegiate Division, 1970-1991 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Division of Social Sciences- Dean of the Faculty, 1973-1991 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Department Announcements, 1989-1991 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Insurance Travel Authorization, 1972-1991 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Field School, 1980-1991 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Public Service (Lithuania), 1991 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Department Conference (Pre-AAA Meetings),, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Chairmanship, 1969-1991 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Admissions Packet, 1989-1992 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Colloquium on Gender, Race, Class, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Surveys, Questionnaires and Other Eternalia, 1972-1992 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Tinker Professor, 1980-1992 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Committee on University Security, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Department of Telecommunications, 1981-1992 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - University Directory, 1987-1992 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Meetings, Minutes I, 1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Meetings, Minutes II, 1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Meetings, Minutes, Memos, 1992-1993 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Division of Social Sciences, Annual Report to the Dean 1975-1993 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - College, Report of the Council on Teaching, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - University-Honorary Degrees II, 1990-1993 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Film Studies Center, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Chronicle, 1973-1993 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Office of the President, 1979-1993 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Committees, 1969-1993 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Committee on the 50th Anniversary, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Committee Assignments, 1974-1993 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Student Faculty Liaison Committee, 1979-1993 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1979-1993 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Recent Publications, 1991-1993 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Departmental Announcements, 1991-1993 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Leaves of Absence (Faculty), 1992-1993 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Requests for Information, 1972-1993 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Student Teaching, 1991-1993 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Department Sponsored Events, 1981-1993 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Leaves of Absence and Assignment to Research, 1975, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Gender, Race, Class, Colloquium, 1992-1993 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Legal Suits, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Computers, 1985-1993 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Departmental Conference, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Residence and Teaching Plans, 1965-1993 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Reports, 1972-1993 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Meetings, Minutes, Memos, 1993-1994 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Lecture Series ‘Founders of Modern Anthropology,' 1995 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Department. Announcements, 1993-1995 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Fire Safety Review, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Work Order Desk Questionnaire, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Senate List, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Risk Assessment Survey, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, Memos, 1994-1995 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Long Range Planning, 1989-1991 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - American Anthropological Association, 1994-1996 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies in Socio-Cultural and Linguistic Anthropology, 1980-1997 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Statement about the Department, undated (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - University- Housing Services, undated (Box 70, Folder 14)
- Series VIII: Faculty and Staff
  - Krogman, Wilton Marion, 1939-1947 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Evans-Pritchard, E.E. 1947-1949 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Godfrey, William S. 1950 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Salz, Beate R. 1953-1954 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Krader, Lawrence, 1956-1957 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Balandier, Georges, 1957-1958 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Blanc, Alberto, 1958-1959 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Nakane, Chie, 1958-1959 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Peristiany, John G. 1958-1959 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Pope, Betty L. 1954-1959 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Rietz, Robert Wilbur, 1954-1959 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Force, Roland 1958-1960 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Holas, B. Theophile, 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Hopper, William David, 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Jacobs, Alan- NSF G13262, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Kroeber, Alfred L. 1958-1960 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Gearing, Fred O. 1955-1961 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Jelinek, Arthur J. 1958-1961 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Lurie, Nancy Oestreich, 1958-1961 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Quimby, George I. 1950-1961 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Goldschmidt, Ernst, 1958-1962 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Hoijer, Harry, 1939, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Maruchi, Toichi, 1959-1962 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Pericot, Garcia Luis, 1960-1962 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Leacock, Seth, 1958-1963 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Moberg, Carl-Axel, 1961-1963 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Shah, A.M. 1960-1963 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Southall, Aidan W. 1961-1963 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Swartz, Marc J. 1960-1963 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Faculty [Department.], 1955-1963 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Bailey, F.G. 1962-1964 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Kleindienst, Maxine R. 1961-1964 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Meggitt, Mervyn 1964 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Millon, Rene, 1961,1964 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Spoehr, Alexander, 1947-1964 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Bateson, Gregory, 1958-1965 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Binford, Lewis R. 1961-1965 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Ekvall, Robert B. Research Associate, 1964-1965 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Greenberg, Joseph H. 1964-1965 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Hester, Evett D. 1951-1965 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Hoben, Allan 1964-1965 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Malik, Subhash Chandra, 1962-1965 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Starr, Frederick- Publisher's Agreement, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Deetz, James, 1965-1966 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Garvin, Paul, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Richards, Audrey I. 1964-1966 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Condon, William S. [Post-doc], 1964-1966 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Hanihara, Kazuro, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Hazlehurst, Leighton, 1965-1967 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Reinman, Fred M. 1965-1967 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Shepardson, Mary T. 1962-1967 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Swift, Michael G. 1963-1967 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Beck, Brenda, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Duncan, Starkey, 1966-1968 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Reports and Recommendations re: Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Frantz, Charles- Research Associate, 1958-1968 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Frisch, John E. 1968 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Spiro, Melford E. 1962-1968 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Evaluation, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Shack, William A. 1966-1969 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Barnett, Stephen, 1969-1970 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Becker (Basso), Ellen, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Merbs, Charles III, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Otten, Charlotte, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Firth, Raymond, 1968-1971 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Hickey, Gerald C. 1971 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Lewis, Phillip, 1970-1971 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Otten, Charlotte, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Saheki, Masatomo, 1970-1971 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Shimizu, Kenji, 1970-1971 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Brocke, Mary (Sister), Post-Doc, 1971-1972 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Ingham, John- Post-Doc, 1971-1972 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Kaut, Charles Raymond, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Kay, Martin, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Parsons, Talcott, 1971-1972 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Parsons, Talcott, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Pitt-Rivers, Julian, 1969-1972 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Yalman, Nur, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action, 1972-1973 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Fisher, Lawrence E. Post-Doctoral, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Forman, Shepard, 1969-1973 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Forman, Shepard, Tenure Review, 1971-1973 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Forman, Shepard, 1970-1973 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Fortes, Meyer, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Fortes, Meyer, 1953-1973 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Jayawardena, Chandra, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Merbs, Charles I, 1969-1973 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Merbs, Charles II, 1967-1973 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Shapiro, Judith, III, 1972-1973 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Shapiro, Judith IV, 1968, 1972-1973 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Topper, Martin D. [Post-doc], 1972-1973 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Cole, Glen- Research Associate, 1956-1974 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Evers, Lawrence (Larry), Post Doctoral Fellow, 1971-1974 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Forman, Shepard, 1973-1974 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Gluckman, Max, 1962-1974 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Houlberg, Marilyn Hammerley, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Hunt, (Muriel) Eva, 1960-1974 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Krasnow, Michael, Post Doc, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - McHenry, Henry, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - McHenry, Henry, Visiting Assistant Professor, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Phillips, J.L. 1974 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Starr, Kenneth, 1962-1974 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Struever, Stuart M. 1970-1974 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Graber, Thomas, 1970-1975 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Placement, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Muller, Tommy, 1970-1975 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Shapiro, Judith R. 1970-1975 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action, 1972-1976 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action, 1972-1976 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Cole, Donald P. Visiting Associate Professor, 1974-1976 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Employment Requisitions, 1968-1976 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Levine, Robert A. 1960-1976 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Levine, Robert A. 1968-1976 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Yen, Douglas, 1975-1976 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Antoun, Richard T. 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Cole, Donald, 1975-1977 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Graber, Thomas M. 1971-1977 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Haviland, John B. 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action, 1973-1978 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Ashum Program, 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Haviland, John B. 1976-1978 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - McLendon, Sally, 1976-1978 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Nominations for visiting Appointments, 1976-1978 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Oxnard, Charles E. 1968-1978 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Crapanzano, Vincent, Visiting Professor, 1977-1979 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Crihfield, Liza- Associated Faculty, 1977-1979 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Secretarial Staff, 1963, 1973-1979 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Appointments, 1976-1980 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Galey, Jean-Claude- Visiting Associate Professor, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Seeger, Anthony, 1970-1980 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Shapiro, Judith, 1978-1980 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Khuri, Fuad, 1970, 1974, 1981-1982 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Magannon, Esteban T., Research Associate, 1980-1982 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Martin, Paul S. 1933-1982 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Appointments, 1978-1983 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Beck, Benjamin B., Research Associate, 1973-1983 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Collier, Malcolm, Research Associate, 1959-1983 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Linguistic Anthro Search, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Traube, Elizabeth, 1970-1983 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Armillas, Pedro, 1964-1984 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Hecht, Susanna- Visiting Assistant Professor of Geography, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Moseley, Michael E. 1980-1985 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Radinsky, Leonard, 1977-1985 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action, 1975-1986 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Department Staff (Clerical, Secretarial, non-Academic), 1968-1991 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Tenure Reviews, Non-Anthropology appointments, 1987-1993 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- Series IX: Finance
  - Subseries 1: Department Budgets
    - Financial Accounts, 1925-1939 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Department- Financial Statements, 1945-1946 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Financial Accounts, 1946-1947 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1951-1954 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 1955-1961 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 1961-1962 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1963-1964 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1963-1964 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Budget, 1964-1965 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Budget, Salaries, 1964-1966 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Budget Notes, 1964-1966 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 1965-1966 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 1966-1967 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1966-1967 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Budget Notes, 1967-1968 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Budget Meeting, 1968-1969 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Budget Notes, 1968-1969 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Budget Projections, 1969-1970 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Budget [College], 1969-1970 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Budget, 1969-1973 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Budget, 1973-1976 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Budget, 1976-1980 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Budget- Communications, 1980-1982 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2: Lichtstern Funds and Requests
    - Lichtstern Fund, 1929-1949 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Lichtstern Fund- Security, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Lichtstern Approval Forms [Original and 2 Blanks], 1974 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Lichtstern Fund, 1971-1975 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Lichtstern, 1972-1975 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Lichtstern Fund, 1971-1977 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Lichtstern Committee, 1977-1980 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Lichtstern Committee Annual Reports, 1977-1980 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Lichtstern Fund, 1979-1981 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Lichtstern Fund, Committee Requests/Decisions, 1982-1983 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Lichtstern [Faculty], 1985-1986 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Department. Admin.- Lichtstern Committee, 1968-1987 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Department. Admin.- Lichtstern Committee, 1975-1992 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Lichtstern, [Faculty], 1988-1992 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Lichtstern Requests, 1990-1993 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Lichtstern Requests, 1994-1995 (Box 84, Folder 7)